



www.facebook.com/pavlos.skoupras

Born in Edessa in 1995. Currently an undergraduate student at the Department of Information and Communication Systems Engineering since 2013. Except from Greek speaking well English and French. Main interests are software engineering, IoT applications and robotics. Love to fly, travel and learn.

Education

Cycle Information Management and Intelligent Systems & Information Systems and Entrepreneurship

University of the Aegean - ICSD department

09/2013 - Present

Karlovasi, Samos

Edessa

Technological cycle
1st General Lyceum of Edessa

09/2011 - 06/2013

Work Experience

Application Developer Global NEST

07/2016 - 08/2017

Athens, Greece

The Global Network on Environmental Science and Technology constitutes an international association of scientists, technologists, engineers and other interested groups involved in all scientific and technological aspects of the environment as well as in application techniques aiming at the development of sustainable solutions.

Contact: Lekkas Dimitrios - dlekkas@env.aegean.gr

Al Lab assistand University of the Aegean

10/2014 – Present

Karlovasi, Greece

- Tasks/Achievements
- Member of Aegean Robotics team
- Research Fellow at educational seminars
- Lab hardware administrator

Contact: Kavallieratou Ergina – kavallieratou@aegean.gr

Skills & Competences

Challenge Taker	
Work as a team	\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet
Adaptable	
Love to learn	\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet
Arduino + C	• • • • •
Xcode + Swift	
Android Studio + Java	

Personal Projects

SmartWash (05/2015 - Present)

 Intelligent laundry monitoring and management system using software, hardware and network equipment.

El Greco Humanoid (02/2017 – Present)

 Design a new humanoid robot as Aegean Robotics team, the El Greco humanoid robot which simulates human characteristics and applications of artificial intelligence.

Tracking by Detection Robots (Theoretical and Practical implementation) (01/2017 – 02/2017)

 Study of the basic methodology of tracking and detection by robots, based on published papers. Matlab implementation.

RoboFix (iOS App) (01/2016 - Present)

 An Innovative app about robotics that gives to the user an easy way to build robotic systems via informations about parts compatibilities and robotic products lists, using calculations and web services.

CEST 2017 Conference app (native iOS & Android app) (07/2016 – Present)

 Completely guide for the conveners of CEST2017, using Xcode with Swift and Android studio with Java.

Certificates

Robotic School (10/2014)
ITURO - Robotic Olympics (04/2015)
Entrepreneurship School (11/2016)

Languages

Greek	•	•	•	•
English				0
French		0	0	0